<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Veronica Rivera</title>
    <link>https://vrivera2017.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Veronica Rivera</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 21:30:40 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://vrivera2017.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>https://vrivera2017.github.io/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 21:30:40 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vrivera2017.github.io/publications/</guid>
      <description>Publications Journal Publications Veronica A. Rivera, David T. Lee. I Want to, but First I Need to: Understanding Crowdworkers&amp;rsquo; Career Goals, Challenges, and Tensions. (2021). In the Proceedings of the ACM - Human Computer Interaction (PACM-HCI), to be presented at CSCW 2021.
Sam Nelson, Michael Orrison, Veronica Rivera. Quantum Enhancements and Biquandle Brackets. (2017) In The Journal of Knot Theory and its Ramifications, 26(5).
[PDF]
Sam, Nelson, Veronica Rivera. Quantum Enhancements of Involutory Birack Counting Invariants.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://vrivera2017.github.io/amt-careers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vrivera2017.github.io/amt-careers/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://vrivera2017.github.io/news/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vrivera2017.github.io/news/</guid>
      <description>News Dec. 2020 My paper, &amp;ldquo;I Want to, but First I Need to: Understanding Crowdworkers&amp;rsquo; Career Goals, Challenges, and Tensions&amp;rdquo;, was accepted for publication in PACM HCI and will be presented at CSCW 2021.
Jan. 2020 I was accepted to the Graduate Student Leadership Certificate Program run by the UCSC Division of Graduate Studies
Nov. 2019 I attended the Future of Work(places) workshop at CSCW 2019.
Oct. 2019 My workshop paper, It Takes a Village to Change Jobs: Towards Workplace Relationships That Support Reskilling in Crowdwork was accepted to the Future of Work(places)workshop at CSCW 2019 in Austin, TX.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Research</title>
      <link>https://vrivera2017.github.io/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vrivera2017.github.io/research/</guid>
      <description>Research Projects Career Development and Online Crowdwork   This is an ongoing project in which I seek to understand the career goals of workers on Amazon Mechanical Turk, and how the online on-demand labor platform contributes to unique challenges in developing workers&amp;rsquo; careers overtime. I&#39;m interested in understanding how these challenges may create difficulties for workers who want to transition careers into specialized online freelance work or white-collar jobs in more traditional brick-and-mortar organizations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teaching</title>
      <link>https://vrivera2017.github.io/teaching/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vrivera2017.github.io/teaching/</guid>
      <description>Teaching and Research Mentoring Teaching I have been a Graduate Teaching Assistant over three quarters for the following two courses:
 UC Santa Cruz CMPS 12A Introduction to Programming, Accelerated (Fall 2018) UC Santa Cruz CMPS 5J Introduction to Programming in Java (Winter 2018, Spring 2018) UC Santa Cruz CMPM 178 Human-Centered Design Research (Winter 2021)  For these courses I was involved in leading multiple lab sections each week and holding weekly office hours.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>