<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Veronica Rivera</title>
    <link>https://vrivera2017.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Veronica Rivera</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 21:30:40 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://vrivera2017.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>https://vrivera2017.github.io/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 21:30:40 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vrivera2017.github.io/publications/</guid>
      <description>Publications Ning F. Ma*, Veronica A. Rivera*, Zheng Yao, Dongwook Yoon. Brush it Off: How Women Workers Manage and Cope with Bias and Harassment in Gender-agnostic Gig Platforms. (2022). In the Proceedings of 2022 CHI Conference on Human Factors in Computing Systems. (24.7% acceptance rate)
[PDF]
Veronica A. Rivera, David T. Lee. I Want to, but First I Need to: Understanding Crowdworkers&amp;rsquo; Career Goals, Challenges, and Tensions. (2021). In the Proceedings of the ACM - Human Computer Interaction (PACM-HCI), to be presented at CSCW 2021.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://vrivera2017.github.io/news/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vrivera2017.github.io/news/</guid>
      <description>News Feb. 2022 Our paper, &amp;ldquo;Brush it off&amp;rdquo;: How Women Workers Manage and Cope with Bias and Harassment in Gender-agnostic Gig Platforms, was accepted for publication at CHI 2022.
Dec. 2021 I passed my qualifying exam and am now a PhD Candidate.
June 2020 I was selected as one of the recipients of the ARCS fellowship for the 2021-2022 school year.
Dec. 2020 My paper, I Want to, but First I Need to: Understanding Crowdworkers&amp;rsquo; Career Goals, Challenges, and Tensions, was accepted for publication in PACM HCI and will be presented at CSCW 2021.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://vrivera2017.github.io/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vrivera2017.github.io/research/</guid>
      <description>Research Project Summaries Career Development and Online Crowdwork   This is an ongoing project in which I seek to understand the career goals of workers on Amazon Mechanical Turk, and how the online on-demand labor platform contributes to unique challenges in developing workers&amp;rsquo; careers overtime. I&#39;m interested in understanding how these challenges may create difficulties for workers who want to transition careers into specialized online freelance work or white-collar jobs in more traditional brick-and-mortar organizations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Other Projects</title>
      <link>https://vrivera2017.github.io/other/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vrivera2017.github.io/other/</guid>
      <description>Additional Projects College Scorecard Data Explorer   Application in use. Displaying admissions rate vs. in-state tuition for institutions in CA, FL, NV, and VT.    Motivation: Recently I found that the U.S Department of Education maintains a dataset called the College Scorecard Dataset, which contains aggregate information for various institutions of higher education in the U.S such as costs and admissions statistics. This information could be incredibly useful for students and families, yet it is difficult to parse through and the amount of information is overwhelming.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teaching</title>
      <link>https://vrivera2017.github.io/teaching/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vrivera2017.github.io/teaching/</guid>
      <description>Teaching Course Designer &amp;amp; Instructor  2022   UCSC HCI 220: Ethics and Activism in Tech and Design  Graduate-level course surveying topics related to tech ethics (e.g. race and gender issues, privacy, AI bias) and tech activism (e.g. labor movements). Course topics discussed through a design lens. [site]     Teaching Assistant  2022, 2021   UCSC CMPM 178: Human-Centered Design Research  Upper-division undergraduate course that introduces various methods used in the design-research process.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>