<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Veronica A. Rivera on Veronica Rivera</title>
    <link>https://vrivera2017.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Veronica A. Rivera on Veronica Rivera</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://vrivera2017.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>https://vrivera2017.github.io/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 21:30:40 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vrivera2017.github.io/publications/</guid>
      <description>Publications * denotes co first author.
Peer-Reviewed Journal and Conference Publications Perfect is the Enemy of Good&amp;quot;: The CISO&amp;rsquo;s Role in Enterprise Security as a Business Enabler Kimberly Ruth, Veronica A. Rivera, Gautam Akiwate, Aurore Fass, Patrick Gage Kelley, Kurt Thomas, Zakir Durumeric. CHI 2025
[PDF][ACM DL]
Safer Algorithmically-Mediated Offline Introductions: Harms and Protective Behaviors Veronica A. Rivera, Daricia Wilkinson, Aurelia Augusta, Sophie Li, Elissa M. Redmiles, Angelika Strohmayer. CSCW 2024 [PDF][ACM DL]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://vrivera2017.github.io/news/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vrivera2017.github.io/news/</guid>
      <description>News June 2023 I participated in the Workshop on Security and Human Behavior at Carnegie Mellon University
May 2023 I successfully defended my dissertation at UC Santa Cruz!
Feb. 2023 I accepted a postion as an Embedded Ethics Postdoctoral Fellow at Stanford University
Sept. 2022 I participated in the Inclusive Security by Design workshop at Mensch und Computer (MuC) conference in Darmstadt, Germany.
July 2022 I started as a visiting researcher at the Max Planck Institute for Software Systems in Saarbrücken, Germany.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://vrivera2017.github.io/other/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vrivera2017.github.io/other/</guid>
      <description>Additional Projects College Scorecard Data Explorer Application in use. Displaying admissions rate vs. in-state tuition for institutions in CA, FL, NV, and VT. Motivation: Recently I found that the U.S Department of Education maintains a dataset called the College Scorecard Dataset, which contains aggregate information for various institutions of higher education in the U.S such as costs and admissions statistics. This information could be incredibly useful for students and families, yet it is difficult to parse through and the amount of information is overwhelming.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://vrivera2017.github.io/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vrivera2017.github.io/research/</guid>
      <description>Research Project Summaries Career Development and Online Crowdwork This is an ongoing project in which I seek to understand the career goals of workers on Amazon Mechanical Turk, and how the online on-demand labor platform contributes to unique challenges in developing workers&amp;rsquo; careers overtime. I&amp;rsquo;m interested in understanding how these challenges may create difficulties for workers who want to transition careers into specialized online freelance work or white-collar jobs in more traditional brick-and-mortar organizations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Service</title>
      <link>https://vrivera2017.github.io/service/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vrivera2017.github.io/service/</guid>
      <description>Service Program Committee USENIX Security: 2026, 2025 CHI (Associate Chair): 2026 CSCW (Associate Chair): 2024 External Reviewer USENIX Security: 2024 (subreviewer) CSCW: 2024 (outstanding reviewer x3), 2021 (outstanding reviewer), 2020, 2019 CHI: 2022 New Media and Society: 2023 Human-Computer Interaction Journal: 2019 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Talks</title>
      <link>https://vrivera2017.github.io/talks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vrivera2017.github.io/talks/</guid>
      <description>Talks Digital Safety: A Problem at the Intersection of Security, Engineering, and Society Harvey Mudd College: June 2025 [slides] Digital Safety Beyond the Platform Carnegie Mellon University: May 2025 Ithaca College: April 2025 Georgia Institute of Technology: April 2025 University of Virginia: April 2025 Cornell University: March 2025 University of Toronto: March 2025 University of California, Los Angeles: March 2025 University of Oregon: February 2025 Safety in Algorithmically-Mediated Offline Introductions Stanford Computer Forum Security Workshop: April 2024 [video] Stanford HAI Fellows Workshop: March 2024 PRISM NSF Site Visit: March 2024 Georgetown University Massive Data Institute Tea Time: February 2024 University of Maryland HCIL Brown Bag Lunch Seminar: February 2024 [video] Stanford University HCI Lunch: February 2024 Safety in Algorithmically-Mediated Offline Introductions: Lessons for Research, Design, and Policy Stanford Women in CS Meeting: May 2024 Stanford Tech Ethics and Policy Career Pathways: May 2024 [slides] Post-Digital Safety in Digitally-Mediated Offline Interactions UC San Diego HCI Seminar: March 2023 Stanford University Security Lunch: February 2023 Stanford University Computing and Society Seminar: January 2023 Mensch und Computer Workshop on Inclusive Security by Design: September 2022 Long-Term Worker Well-Being in the Future of Work Stanford University HCI Lunch: April 2022 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teaching</title>
      <link>https://vrivera2017.github.io/teaching/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vrivera2017.github.io/teaching/</guid>
      <description>Teaching Stanford Most of my teaching at Stanford was done in the context of the Embedded Ethics program. I led teams of CS faculty and teaching assistants to create and teach ethics curriculum in CS courses. Some of our materials are open source on the Embedded Ethics website. Please reach out to me if you are interested in seeing additional material for the courses I led below.
Ethics Curriculum 2023, 2024 (x2), 2025 CS 221: Artificial Intelligence: Principles and Techniques Large intro-level AI course.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
