<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Veronica Rivera</title>
    <link>https://vrivera2017.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Veronica Rivera</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://vrivera2017.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>https://vrivera2017.github.io/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 21:30:40 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vrivera2017.github.io/publications/</guid>
      <description>Publications Peer-Reviewed Journal and Conference Publications * indicates equal contribution, listed in alphabetical order by last name.
I publish primarily in computer science journals and conference proceedings, where authors are listed in order of contribution. Some of my early work is published in math journals, where authors are listed alphabetically
Safer Algorithmically-Mediated Offline Introductions: Harms and Protective Behaviors Veronica A. Rivera, Daricia Wilkinson, Aurelia Augusta, Sophie Li, Elissa M. Redmiles, Angelika Strohmayer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://vrivera2017.github.io/news/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vrivera2017.github.io/news/</guid>
      <description>News June 2023 I participated in the Workshop on Security and Human Behavior at Carnegie Mellon University
May 2023 I successfully defended my dissertation at UC Santa Cruz!
Feb. 2023 I accepted a postion as an Embedded Ethics Postdoctoral Fellow at Stanford University
Sept. 2022 I participated in the Inclusive Security by Design workshop at Mensch und Computer (MuC) conference in Darmstadt, Germany.
July 2022 I started as a visiting researcher at the Max Planck Institute for Software Systems in Saarbrücken, Germany.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://vrivera2017.github.io/other/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vrivera2017.github.io/other/</guid>
      <description>Additional Projects College Scorecard Data Explorer Application in use. Displaying admissions rate vs. in-state tuition for institutions in CA, FL, NV, and VT. Motivation: Recently I found that the U.S Department of Education maintains a dataset called the College Scorecard Dataset, which contains aggregate information for various institutions of higher education in the U.S such as costs and admissions statistics. This information could be incredibly useful for students and families, yet it is difficult to parse through and the amount of information is overwhelming.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://vrivera2017.github.io/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vrivera2017.github.io/research/</guid>
      <description>Research Project Summaries Career Development and Online Crowdwork This is an ongoing project in which I seek to understand the career goals of workers on Amazon Mechanical Turk, and how the online on-demand labor platform contributes to unique challenges in developing workers&amp;rsquo; careers overtime. I&amp;rsquo;m interested in understanding how these challenges may create difficulties for workers who want to transition careers into specialized online freelance work or white-collar jobs in more traditional brick-and-mortar organizations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teaching</title>
      <link>https://vrivera2017.github.io/teaching/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vrivera2017.github.io/teaching/</guid>
      <description>Teaching Stanford Ethics Curriculum Developer &amp;amp; Instructor 2023, 2024 (x2) CS 221: Artificial Intelligence: Principles and Techniques Intro-level computer systems Large intro-level AI course Ethics Curriculum Developer &amp;amp; Instructor 2023 CS 177: Human-Centered Product Management Intro-level computer systems Product management course focusing on design, organizational, and interpersonal skills Ethics Curriculum Developer &amp;amp; Instructor 2024 CS 124: From Language to Information Intro-level computer systems Intro-level NLP course Ethics Curriculum Developer &amp;amp; Instructor 2023, 2024 (x2) CS 107: Computer Organization and Systems Intro-level computer systems Ethics Curriculum Developer &amp;amp; Instructor 2024 (x2) CS 106B: Programming Abstractions Second course in the Stanford CS sequence, focus on object-oriented programming, data structures, and run-time.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
