<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Veronica Rivera</title>
    <link>https://vrivera2017.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Veronica Rivera</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 21:30:40 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://vrivera2017.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>https://vrivera2017.github.io/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 21:30:40 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vrivera2017.github.io/publications/</guid>
      <description>Publications Journal Publications Nelson, Sam., Orrison, Michael., Rivera, Veronica. (2017). Quantum Enhancements and Biquandle Brackets. The Journal of Knot Theory and its Ramifications, 26(5).
Nelson, Sam., Rivera, Veronica. (2014). Quantum Enhancements of Involutory Birack Counting Invariants. The Journal of Knot Theory and its Ramifications, 23(7).
Conference Publications Tenorio, D., Rivera, V., Medina, J., Leondar, A., Gaumer, M., Dodds, Z. (2015). Visual Autonomy via 2D Matching in Rendered 3D Models. In Proceedings of the 11th International Symposium on Visual Computing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://vrivera2017.github.io/news/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vrivera2017.github.io/news/</guid>
      <description>News Jan. 2020 I was accepted to the Graduate Student Leadership Certificate Program run by the UCSC Division of Graduate Studies
Nov. 2019 I attended the Future of Work(places) workshop at CSCW 2019.
Oct. 2019 My workshop paper, It Takes a Village to Change Jobs: Towards Workplace Relationships That Support Reskilling in Crowdwork was accepted to the Future of Work(places)workshop at CSCW 2019 in Austin, TX.
June 2019 I attended the Human-Computer Interaction Consortium (HCIC) conference on the Futures of Work in Watsonville, California as 1 of 2 PhD students selected to represent UC Santa Cruz.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Research</title>
      <link>https://vrivera2017.github.io/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vrivera2017.github.io/research/</guid>
      <description>Research Projects Career Development and Online Crowdwork   This is an ongoing project in which I seek to understand the career goals of workers on Amazon Mechanical Turk, and how the online on-demand labor platform contributes to unique challenges in developing workers&amp;rsquo; careers overtime. I&#39;m interested in understanding how these challenges may create difficulties for workers who want to transition careers into specialized online freelance work or white-collar jobs in more traditional brick-and-mortar organizations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teaching</title>
      <link>https://vrivera2017.github.io/teaching/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vrivera2017.github.io/teaching/</guid>
      <description>Teaching and Research Mentoring Teaching I have been a Graduate Teaching Assistant over three quarters for the following two courses:
 UC Santa Cruz CMPS 12A Introduction to Programming, Accelerated (Fall 2018) UC Santa Cruz CMPS 5J Introduction to Programming in Java (Winter 2018, Spring 2018)  For both of these courses I was involved in leading multiple lab sections each week and holding weekly office hours. I helped students with lab and homework assignments, and helped them prepare for quizzes and exams.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>